Hrvoje Sesar

Backend Developer

- B category Croatian In linkedin.com/in/hrvoje-sesar-693034265 C github.com/hrvojesesar

Education

2019 - 2024

Employment

Jul 2024 - Current

Apr 2023 - Jul 2024

Skills

Projects

Profile

Bachelor's and Master's degrees in Computing

Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Computing and Electrical Engineering, University of Mostar, Mostar

Remote Freelancer

Upwork Global Inc.

- Working on E-commerce, Backoffice, ERP, SaaS web applications, API integration
- Using technologies such as: .NET, SQL Server, Laravel, MySQL
- Solving complex problems, including performance optimization, third-pary integrations, etc.
- Maintaining consistent communication with clients to define requirements and track progress
- Preparing technical documentation for delivered projects

Junior Software Developer

Diplomat Tech d.o.o., Široki Brijeg

- Developing modular applications as part of larger software ecosystem
- Using technologies: .NET, MS SQL Server, Redis
- Additional refinement on Backend
- Fixing bugs, tasks, code refactoring
- Project documentation
- Agile Development with Scrum and Jira

C#/.NET	JavaScript	MS SQL Server	OOP	Git
PHP/Laravel	HTM5/CSS3	MySQL	REST API	MS Office
Java	Bootstrap	PostgreSQL	Microservices	Soft Skills
С		Redis	Server Side	English

- Online Pharmacy
- Contacts List
- Weather App
- Finance Management App

- Online Learning Room
- Trip Harmony
- SportPro Backoffice
- Fleet Management App

Backend Developer with proven student internship and work experience helping companies create and maintain a better reusable codebase. Ability to continuously learn and gain experience from senior developers and through various courses. Experience on projects within the faculty doing Backend and Frontend. Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills to more complex and larger projects. I consider myself an ambitious, creative, and communicative person, open to new challenges and opportunities to grow and learn. Experience with teamwork/group work.